<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>how-to on Velero</title>
    <link>/tags/how-to/</link>
    <description>Recent content in how-to on Velero</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Velero v1.1 backing up and restoring Stateful apps on vSphere</title>
      <link>/blog/Velero-v1-1-Stateful-Backup-vSphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/Velero-v1-1-Stateful-Backup-vSphere/</guid>
      <description>Velero version 1.1 provides support to backup applications orchestrated on upstream Kubernetes running natively on vSphere. This post will provide detailed information on how to use Velero v1.1 to backup and restore a stateful application (Cassandra) that is running in a Kubernetes cluster deployed on vSphere. At this time there is no vSphere plugin for snapshotting stateful applications during a Velero backup. In this case, we rely on a third party program called restic to copy the data contents from Persistent Volumes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Velero v1.1 backing up and restoring apps on vSphere</title>
      <link>/blog/Velero-v1-1-on-vSphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/Velero-v1-1-on-vSphere/</guid>
      <description>Velero version 1.1 provides support to backup Kubernetes applications deployed on vSphere. This post will provide detailed information on how to install and configure Velero to backup and restore a stateless application (nginx) that is running in Kubernetes on vSphere. At this time there is no vSphere plugin for snapshotting stateful applications on vSphere during a Velero backup. In this case, we rely on a third party program called restic. However this post does not include an example of how to backup a stateful application.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>