<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steve Kriss on Velero</title>
    <link>/tags/Steve-Kriss/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Steve Kriss on Velero</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/Steve-Kriss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Velero 1.3: Improved CRD Backups/Restores, Multi-Arch Docker Images, and More!</title>
      <link>/blog/Velero-1.3-Voyage-Continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/Velero-1.3-Voyage-Continues/</guid>
      <description>Velero’s voyage continues with the release of version 1.3, which includes improvements to CRD backups and restores, multi-arch Docker images including support for arm/arm64 and ppc64le, and many other usability and stability enhancements. This release includes significant contributions by community members, and we’re thrilled to be able to partner with you all in continuing to improve Velero.
Let’s take a deeper look at some of this release’s highlights.
Custom Resource Definition Backup and Restore Improvements This release includes a number of related bug fixes and improvements to how Velero backs up and restores custom resource definitions (CRDs) and instances of those CRDs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Velero 1.2 Sets Sail by Shifting Plugins Out of Tree, Adding a Structural Schema, and Sharpening Usability</title>
      <link>/blog/Velero-1.2-Sets-Sail/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/Velero-1.2-Sets-Sail/</guid>
      <description>Velero continues to evolve with the release of version 1.2. With this release, we’ve focused on extracting in-tree cloud provider plugins into their own repositories, making further usability improvements to the restic integration, preparing for the general availability of Kubernetes custom resource definitions (CRDs) by adding a structural schema to our CRDs, and many other new features and usability improvements.
Let’s take a look at the highlights for this release.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>