<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nolan Brubaker on Velero</title>
    <link>/tags/Nolan-Brubaker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nolan Brubaker on Velero</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/Nolan-Brubaker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Velero 1.4: Introducing Beta CSI Support, Backup Progress Tracking, and Much More!</title>
      <link>/blog/Velero-1.4-Community-Wave/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/Velero-1.4-Community-Wave/</guid>
      <description>The Velero team is excited to announce the launch of Velero v1.4.0! This release is one of our largest since v1.0.0, with many of our new features coming from community contributors.
Beta CSI Support Velero v1.4.0 now extends Velero’s support for snapshotting beyond Velero’s native VolumeSnapshotter plugins to include beta support for the Kubernetes Container Storage Interface volume snapshotting capabilities.
The Container Storage Interface (CSI) is a way for container orchestrators such as Kubernetes to provide a standard interface for storage systems, without having to create drivers for each orchestration system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Velero 1.1: Improved restic Support and More Visibility</title>
      <link>/blog/announcing-velero-1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/announcing-velero-1.1/</guid>
      <description>We’ve made big strides in improving Velero. Since our release of version 1.0 in May 2019, we have been hard at work improving our restic support and planning for the future of Velero. In addition, we’ve seen some helpful contributions from the community that will make life easier for all of our users. Also, the Velero community has reached 100 contributors!
For this release, we’ve focused on improving Velero’s restic integration: making repository locks shorter lived, giving more visibility into restic repositories when migrating clusters, and expanding support to more volume types.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>